addicted.com 2015-11-21

# Privacy Policy

###  ADDICTED.COM PRIVACY POLICY  

EFFECTIVE DATE: September 20, 2007

  1. **1\. Introduction**

Addicted.com LLC (“us,” “we,” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Company Website (“the Site”). We created this Website Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review those privacy policies. 

  2. **2\. Information Collection Practices**

    1. 2.1 Types of Information Collected 

      1. _2.1.1 Traffic Data Collected_

We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain names; (3) domain servers; (4) access times; (5) types of computers accessing the Site; and (6) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We may also use “cookies” to customize content specific to your interests and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to your computer. Using cookies can enhance your experience of the Site. However, you have the ability to accept or decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully utilize the interactive features of the Site. 

      2. _2.1.2 Personal Information Collected_

In order for you to access certain services such as creating a user profile, uploading videos, posting messages in our forums or in the video comments section, entering contests, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to news letters or other mailing lists that we offer via the Site, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, and e-mail address) and (2) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, age, and occupation). 

    2. 2.2 Uses of Information Collected 

      1. _2.2.1 Company Use of Information_

We may use your Personal Information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Site. We do not use your email address or other Personal Information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent, except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Site changes or for customer service purposes). 

We use both your Personal Information and certain Traffic Data to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends. 

      2. _2.2.2 Sharing of Personal Information_

Except as explained herein, we do not share your Personal Information with third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We only disclose your Personal Information to our service providers who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, monitoring, fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Site. Those service providers have all agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to Company. 

We reserve the right to share or transfer your Personal Information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Company or substantially all of Company’s assets. 

      3. _2.2.3 User Choice Regarding Collection of Personal Information_

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personal Information. 

  3. **3\. Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information**

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Use. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit your Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser. 

    1. 3.1 User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information 

We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date. At any time, you may, visit your personal profile at http://www.addicted.com/forums. Through your personal profile you may review and update you Personal Information that we have already collected. 

    2. 3.2 Lost or Stolen Information 

You must promptly notify us if your user name or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that user name or password from your account and update our records accordingly. 

    3. 3.3 Public Information 

The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We may also make chat rooms, video uploading, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information. 

  4. **4\. Contacting Us and Policy Updates**

    1. 4.1 User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information 

If you have any questions about this Policy, our privacy practices related to this Site, or if you would like us to remove your information from our database please feel free to contact us at [privacy@addicted.com](mailto:privacy@addicted.com). 

    2. 4.2 Lost or Stolen Information 

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. 

  * ### Find Help Now

Enter your ZIP to find help nearest you:

  * ### Contact Us For Support

  * ### How Is Obamacare Affecting Addiction?

  * ### Did You Know?

"54 percent of high school seniors do not think regular steroid use is harmful, the lowest number since 1980, when the National Institute on Drug Abuse started asking about perception on steroids." — [http://www.dosomething.org](http://www.dosomething.org/)

Next »
